

HI, I'M JEFF

I specialize in product strategy and engineering leadership for startups and hyper-growth companies that want to build, launch, and rapidly iterate mobile apps and cloud-native products.

I approach work from the perspective that technology should solve important problems, increase the quality of life, and do so in an engaging and enjoyable way. I am most satisfied when working on challenging, high-value issues with people who deeply care about their work.

I rely on my experience as a principal software engineer and product manager, which provides a solid platform for leadership and mentoring. I have expertise in Flutter, IOS, cloud-native architectures, Agile methodologies, product strategy, and leadership.

My work is complemented by an active personal life centered around family adventures, many of which are outdoors, either around Naples, where we live or in the Rocky Mountains, where we occasionally travel during the summer. I also enjoy tooling on German-engineered automobiles, riding motorcycles, and paddle-boarding.

I look forward to bringing my leadership, enthusiasm, and technical expertise to your organization.

gol Zahan



JEFF HIGHAM

Principal Software Engineer Flutter • IOS • React

(305) 570-0916

☑ https://bio.link/jeffhigham

@jeffhigham

@jeffhigham-f3

I specialize in product strategy and engineering leadership for startups and hyper-growth companies that want to build, launch, and rapidly iterate mobile apps and cloud-native products. My expertise as a principal software engineer and product manager provides a solid platform for leadership and mentoring.

WORK EXPERIENCE



Principal Software Developer

FasCat Coaching

May 2022 - Present · Boulder, CO



Senior Systems Engineer

Viasat Inc

Nov 2007 - October 2011 · Englewood, CO



Founder // Principal Developer F3 Software

Jan 2009 - Present · Naples, FL



Senior Systems Engineer

Comcast

Jun 2007 - Nov 2007 · Englewood, CO



Senior Director of Engineering

Verb Technology, Inc

Mar 2015 - May 2022 · Newport Beach, CA



Senior Systems Engineer

EDS Advanced Solutions

Mar 2006 - Jun 2007 · Broomfield, CO



Software Developer

Goodwin Media

Jan 2013 - July 2019 · Highland, UT



Software Developer

Nine Systems/Akamai

Dec 2004 - Mar 2006 · Englewood, CO



Senior Software Engineer

Oracle

October 2011 - Mar 2013 · Austin, TX



UNIX Systems Admin

Earthlink

2002 - 2004 · Englewood, CO

EXPERTISE



Flutter &



IOS &



ANDROID



REACT

FIREBASE



AWS



GOOGLE CLOUD



LE AGILE
D METHODOLOGIES



CONTINUOUS INTEGRATION



MENTORING

EDUCATION



University of Colorado Computer Science 2000 - 2003



University of Utah Human Biology 1998 - 2000